- I don't see anything at all, Sheldon.
- Ugh.
You're the doctor, but I'm constantly
hearing this annoying sound.
(Leonard:)Me too.
(Sheldon:)Is it a high-frequency whistle?
(Leonard:)No, it's more of a relentless,
narcissistic drone.
Yeah, there's no inflammation at all,
Sheldon.
Then it must be a tumor.
(Steph:)I seriously doubt it.
(Leonard:)Maybe it's a lingering bacterial infection
from all those childhood toilet swirlies.
(Sheldon:)Is that possible?
I used to get those all the time.
(Sheldon:)Even in church.
(Steph:)Well, you know, if it is from a swirly,
there's something I can do, okay. Ahem.
(Steph:)Circle, circle, dot, dot,
now you have a cootie shot.
(Steph:)- I'm going to bed.
- Okay.
(Leonard:)- I'll be right in.
It's not enough she mocks me...
(Sheldon:)...but that isn't even the correct procedure
for a cootie shot.